{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What was significant about Italy's 2-1 win against Albania in Group B?",
      "options": [
        "It was Italy's 50th victory in a EURO finals",
        "Albania scored the fastest-ever EURO goal",
        "There were more shots than any other game is EURO history",
        "Italy scored the latest-ever EURO goal"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Georgia appeared at a major international tournament for the very first time. Who did their one and only victory at EURO 2024 come against?",
      "options": ["Czechia", "Turkey", "Spain", "Portugal"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which goalkeeper saved all three penalties in a shoot-out during his team's round of 16 victory?",
      "options": [
        "Mike Maignan (France)",
        "Jordan Pickford (England)",
        "Diogo Costa (Portugal)",
        "Unai Simon (Spain)"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose winner after 89 minutes 59 seconds was the latest ever scored in the semi-finals of a EURO or World Cup (excluding extra time)?",
      "options": [
        "Dani Olmo (Spain)",
        "Ollie Watkina (England)",
        "Lamine Yamal (Spain)",
        "Harry Kane (England)"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Spain beat England 2-1 in the final in Berlin. Who scored the winning goal?",
      "options": [
        "Lamine Yamal",
        "Nico Williams",
        "Mike Merino",
        "Mikel Oyarzabal"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Spain's 15 goals at EURO 2024 is a new tournament record. Which team did they surpass? ",
      "options": ["Germany", "France", "England", "Portugal"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player attempted the most shots at EURO 2024 with a total of 24?",
      "options": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Kai Havertz",
        "Kylian Mbappe",
        "Memphis Depay"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which side had the most overall average possession in the tournament with a total of 64.8%?",
      "options": ["Netherlands", "Italy", "England", "Portugal"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "A total of how many goals were scored at the tournament? ",
      "options": ["95", "117", "128", "133"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country hosted the EURO 2024?",
      "options": ["Germany", "Belgium", "France", "Denmark"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who scored Euro 2024's first goal?",
      "options": [
        "Kai Havertz",
        "Jamal Musiala",
        "Florian Wirtz",
        "Niclas Fullkrug"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "The Czech Republic v Turkey game set a new record for the most cards in a Euros match. How many cards (both yellow and red) were dished out?",
      "options": ["12", "15", "18", "21"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who holds the all-time Euro goals record?",
      "options": [
        "Harry Kane",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Nico Williams",
        "Lamine Yamal"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player appeared in a record 6th Euro tournament at EURO 2024?",
      "options": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Toni Kroos",
        "Luka Modric",
        "Kylian Mbappe"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many time England won EURO title?",
      "options": ["1", "3", "0", "5"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
